下句已做修改
午後十時四十八分　今日もあの人は来なかった
---------------------------------------------
やはりあの女はカレーを作るために呼ばれた
カレー女に過ぎなかったのだ
10:48 PM.
She didn't show up today either.
She was nothing more than a Curry Girl called to make curry, after all.
勝ったはね
まだ何か企んでるの
勝 手に入って来ないでよ
勝手に人の物を見るなって　何度言ったら分かるのよ
I've won.
Are you up to no good again?
あのさ　こんなこといつまで続けるつもり
Who said you can come in?!
計画が終了するまでよ
How many times do I have to tell you to not peek at my stuff?
言ったでしょう　プロジェクトM
そのプロジェクトMって
So, how long are you going to keep this up?
Just Married
マリッジ　結婚するのMとかじゃないよね
Until I accomplish my mission.
んなわけないじゃない
Project M, remember?
そう　そうだよね
That "Project M" doesn't mean "marriage," as in getting married, right?
プロジェクトMは壮大でクリエーティブな計画なの
クリエーティブ
Of course not!
R-Right!
Project M is a grand and creative plan!
多蕗さん　今頃何してるのかな
Creative?
独身なんだから
夜はネットでエッチな画像でも見てるじゃないの
多蕗さんはそういうのは見ないわ
Tabuki...
如何だか
I wonder what you're doing now?
いつまでいるの　さっさと帰れば
He's single, so he probably looks at internet porn at night!
何も
Tabuki doesn't look at that kind of thing.
僕だって好き好んでここにいるわけじゃ
Yeah, right.
多蕗さんが何をしていたか　分かったわ
How long are you going to stay here?
Why don't you leave already?
メールよ　私にラブレター書いてたのよ
It's not like...
It's not like I want to be here.
くるくる回る
I found out what Tabuki was doing.
君の瞳探して回る
He was writing an email.
駅のホーム
A love letter to me!
響くファンファーレ
<< kurukuru mawaru kimi no hitomi >>
<< Round and round, your eyes wander around >>
ガラガラ音を立てる街
<< sagashite mawaru eki no home >>
<< Searching around the station's platforms >>
とりあえず耳を貸してみたの
<< hibiku fanfare >>
<< The sound of fanfare from afar >>
もうすぐ消えるはずの世界に
<< garagara oto wo tateru machi >>
<< The clamorous city making noise >>
<< toriaezu mimi wo kashite ita no >>
<< I tried to keep an ear out for all this >>
<< mousugu kieru hazu no sekai ni >>
<< In a world that's about to end >>
御免ね
もう二度と会えないようなそんな気がして
<< gomen ne >>
<< I'm sorry >>
運命が笑う
<< mou nido to aenai youna sonna ki ga shite >>
<< I just had a feeling I would never see you again >>
臨界点突破してる
限界なら既に去って
<< unmei ga warau >>
<< Fate is laughing at us >>
絶対的支配だって
崩壊
<< rinkaiten toppa shiten da >>
<< I'm already past the point of no return >>
終末理論は机上の空論でしかないって
<< genkai nara sude ni satte >>
<< Far over my limit >>
<< zettaiteki shihai datte >>
<< Even your absolute control has >>
ゼロとイチの世界線の果てから
<< houkai >>
<< Crumbled >>
<< shuumatsu riron wa kijou no kuuron shika naitte >>
<< "The end of the world is nothing but a hypothesis" >>
叫ぶよ
<< 0 to 1 no sekaisen no hate kara sakebu yo >>
<< Is what I'm crying out from other side of the binary world line >>
もうすぐ君が会いにくるような気がして
僕は目を閉じるよ
<< mou sugu kimi ga ai ni kuru you na ki ga shite >>
<< I have a feeling you'll come see me soon >>
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
日听 xHunter 翻译：英英 校对：凌可乐
时间轴：绯桜闲   压制：笑眯眯的妖精
<< boku wa me wo tojiru yo >>
<< So I will be waiting with my eyes closed >>
Would you like to go to the theatre with me next Sunday?
もしよかったら
次の日曜日僕と一緒にお芝居を見に行きませんか
Someone gave me two tickets to a popular show.
人気の舞台のチケット二枚頂いたのです
I'm sure you will enjoy a break from your studies.
勉強の息抜きにきっと楽しめると思いますよ
Oh, Tabuki!
多蕗さんたら
You even made up a story about receiving tickets...
チケットをもらったんだなんて　嘘までついて
All to ask me out on a date!
私もデートに
Yes, you're ready to go.
よし　いけるは
All the way to Destiny!
このまま一気にデスティニー　イエー
Yay!
Sunshiny Troupe
The Tragedy of M
Scatter with Paris
There's unrest even among the soldiers.
兵士達の中にさえ不満が燻っている
Most of them are from poor families.
貧しい家の出の者殆どだからな
The royal family is losing the support of the people.
国民の気持ちが王室から離れてしまった
Excuse my interruption.
お話中　失礼します　王妃様のお見えです
Her Royal Highness is here.
What?
何　マリー様が
Princess Marie is here?
What were you all talking about?
お揃いで何の話かしら
Oh! Here comes Yuri!
おお　百合が出できたぞ
He really wasn't lying about receiving the tickets...
チケットもらったって嘘じゃなかったのね
Oh, my princess!
は　王妃様
If you'd just answer me with an oui,
もしあなたが一言おいとおっしゃってくださるなら
I will put my life at stake to free you from Paris!
わたくしはこの首を賭けてでも
貴方をこのパリから攫って行きましょ
Oh, please forget about me, Comte!
もうわたくしの事はお諦めになって　伯爵
I am the Princess of this country.
マリーはこの国の王妃
I must give up my life to atone for my sins if that is what the citizens want!
タニがそう望むのなら
命を賭けて自らの過ちを償わんにはなりません
What's with this choreography?
何　この演出　古くさい
It's so corny.
What? You're crying?
って　泣くの
The Tragedy of M
Lyrics  Ikami Ikuni
Composition  Yukari Hashimoto
Song  Yuri Tokikago
Paris.
パリ　パリ
麗しいの都　パリ
The City of Light, Paris.
I'm certain you will find me tomorrow morning.
明日の朝きっと　あなたは見つけるでしょう
冷たいしたかみに　散るパラの花
The rose petals scattering like snow flakes.
That is I... Marie.
それは私　マリー
My duty.
私の勉め
My fate.
私の定め
Paris.
パリ　パリ
パリ
いいや　感動しちゃったよ
I'm so moved!
That last line was so touching!
ラストのあのセリフ　よかったな
そ　そうですね
Y-Yes...
Yuri!
We can't even get near her.
これじゃとても近づけないな
Oh, well. Let's go for dinner––just the two of us.
仕方ない　二人だけで食事に行こうか
Just the two of us?
二人だけ
Y-Yes! Let's go with just the two of us!
そ　そうですね　二人だけで行きましょ
Ah, it's from Yuri.
あ　百合からだよ
Wow, she's way ahead of us.
ええ　さすが気が利くな
She already booked a restaurant.
レストラン予約してくれてるだって
"Wait for me there," she says.
先に行って待てて欲しいってさ
What a fancy restaurant!
凄いレストランだ　ちょっと気後れしちゃうね
It makes you nervous, doesn't it?
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
御免なさい　お待たせしたかしら
Look, it's Yuri Tokikago, the actress!
ほら　あれ女優の時籠百合さんよ
Oh, my! She's even more beautiful in person than on TV!
テレビで見るよりずっと綺麗ね
I really wanted you to see me on the stage,
舞台の私をリンゴちゃんにぜひ見て頂きたくて
so I convinced Tabuki invite you.
多蕗君に無理にお願いしちゃった
I hope it wasn't too much of a bother.
ご迷惑じゃなかったかしら
N-No... you were wonderful.
いいえ　とても素敵でした
She's an actress.
この女は女優　優しい笑顔なんてお手の物
She can make a kind smile in her sleep.
Behind her glass mask is her outrageously black heart!
綺麗なガラスの仮面の裏側は人並み外れた腹黒さ
Don't be deceived, Ringo!
だめよ　リンゴ
騙されじゃ
This woman survived through the torrents of show biz.
この女は芸能界の荒波を生き延びてきた
She's a killer whale, a gangster of the sea!
海のギャング　シャジなのよ
She must have devoured countless victims.
これまでもさぼり食ってきた獲物の数は海の泡程
The killer whale woman will do anything!
シャジ女は手段を選ばない
Yuri.
百合　君の瞳に乾杯
Here's looking at you, kid.
Cheers.
乾杯
Oh, dear!
マー　大変　すぐに洗わないと滲みになってしまうわ
We have to wash it right away or it'll stain!
Kingpin
What should I do?
如何しましょう
Kingpin
Tokikago...
時籠君
Kingpin
Say...
ねえ
うん
Don't you think I'm perfect for the lead in the next play?
次の芝居の主役百合にぴったりと思わない
I guess so.
そうだな
Hey...
ねえ
Tokikago...
時籠　君
これはファビュラス　マックス
This is... Fabulous... Max!
Kingpin
I know it.
私には分かる
The killer whale woman must be hunting like that every night!
そんなシャジ女のハンティングが毎夜行われているってことが
This woman's body and soul are both pitch black under her charade!
この女は人皮抜けば　身も心も真っ黒に汚れているのよ
Don't let your guard down, Tabuki!
多蕗さん　油断しないで
How's does the next Sunday sound?
如何　次の日曜日
Huh?
Are you free?
空いてるかな
We're planning for a little party.
実はちょっとしたパーティーを企画しているの
I would love for you to come!
是非リンゴちゃんにもいらっしゃて欲しいわ
You know, with that cute boyfriend...
ほら　この間の可愛い彼氏と
ええと　高倉君って言ったかしら
Takakura, was it?
He's...!
あれは
Not my boyfriend.
彼氏なんかじゃありません
Is that so?
あら　そうなの
Come on, ask Takakura to come with you.
いいじゃないか　高倉も誘ってあげなよ
After all, he's a bird buddy.
あいつは鳥仲間だもんな
Then, it's settled.
なら　そういうことで　決まり
Thank you all for coming today.
皆様ようこそお越しくださいました
Yuri is prettier than ever.
百合さん　今日は一段と輝いてるな
ふん　皆あの女の外面に騙されてるのよ
You've all been deceived by her outer appearance.
Why don't just give it up already?
もういい加減諦めたら
Don't be ridiculous.
馬鹿言わないで
I know Tabuki way better than she does.
私の方が多蕗さんのことよく分かってるだから
Could you pack these red and yellow ones to go?
この赤いのと黄色いのお持ち帰り用に詰めてもらいます
何遣ってんのよ
What are you doing?!
I'm taking some home for Himari.
ひまりにお土産だよ
Ow!
いて
Were you listening to what I said?
先の話ちゃんと聞いた
What?
何
I was talking about her!
あれよ　あの毒蜘蛛
You have to watch that black widow to keep her away from Tabuki!
これ以上多蕗さんに近づけないよう見張るのよ
That's absurd!
んな無茶な
Diary.
日記
I'll do it.
やります
I apologize for the interruption.
I'm sure you're all enjoying the party,
皆様お楽しみのところとは存じますが
but Ms. Yuri Tokikago has an important announcement to make.
これより　時籠百合から大変重要な御知らせがございます
Come on, my love!
come on my love
Thank you all for coming out to my party today.
皆様本日はお忙しい中まことにありがとうございます
I know this is sudden, but there is something I must tell you.
さて　突然ではございますが　皆様にお伝えしなければなりません
By the way, where's Tabuki?
そういえば　多蕗さん何処かしら
I, Yuri Tokikago will retire from Sunshiny Troupe after the next play.
私時籠百合は次の舞台をもちまして
And one more thing.
それからもう一つ
Please allow me to introduce...
皆様にご紹介させていただきます
Who is it?
This is Keiju Tabuki.
こちらは多蕗桂樹さんです
I would like to inform you that we are engaged today.
本日私と彼が婚約をいたしましたことをご報告申し上げます
Congratulations!
おめでとう
おめでとうございます
Thank you!
ありがとう　皆様ありがとうございます
Thank you, everyone!
I will retire from acting to pursue a new beginning with the person I love,
愛する人との新しい気分を機に
舞台を卒業いたしますが
but I will forever treasure the wonderful time I spent on stage at...
そこで得た替え難い宝物胸に
Stop, stop!
ストップ　ストップ
Let's not cry on this joyous occasion.
お祝いの時で湿っぽいのはよそぜ
Now, everyone, please give a round of applause to...
さあ　皆さん
僕の最愛の女房役と彼女を
いや
日記　貸してもらえないかな
Can you let me borrow the diary now?
Today's
Slogan
Tabuki is already engaged to Yuri.
多蕗さんは百合さんと婚約までしちゃったんだし
No.
だめよ
My Project M will not be hindered by something so trivial.
こんなことで私のプロジェクトMは挫折したりしない
I'm the one who's living under the same roof as Tabuki!
多蕗さんと一つ屋根の下に暮らしてるのは私なんだから
Under the same roof? You're just...
一つ屋根の下って　あれは
He and I are destined to be together.
私と彼は結ばれる運命　これは
This is... yes.
そう　ちょっとした愛の試練に過ぎないわ
Nothing more than a test of my love.
By the way...
ところで
What?
何
How old are you now?
貴方　今幾つ
I'm 16...
十六だけど　なんで
Why do you ask?
Know When
to Give Up...
Looks like it's all in there.
確かに
Now we can stay in our home for a while longer.
これでまた暫くはあの家にいられる
Also, only a select few can use this.
それから　こいつを使える人間は限られてる
It really wasn't done by your people?
本当にあれはアンタたちの仕業じゃないんだな
Gosh, I must crush him soon.
嫌だわ　早くすり潰さないと
Yes, understood.
ええ　分かった
I will continue on my end as well.
こちらもこのまま進める
We must complete the Project M at all costs.
プロジェクトMは必ず完成させなければ
That's not nice.
うみ　だめですよ
I'm sorry.
すみません
Don't worry.
大丈夫
I'll just say I forgot to take something home if someone finds us.
もし誰かに見つかっても忘れ物を取りに来たって言えば平気よ
But a high school boy sneaking into all-girls high school at night is totally out of line!
でも　高校生男子が夜の女子高に忍び込むなんて
完全にアウトだろう
Ribbit.
ゲロ
If you want to get closer to a man
Click Now
Entrance
Dulcamara's
Magic Potion Class
Plant
Snake
Frog
Other
Eggchanted Frog
This is...
これ
The same frog.
同じ蛙だ
読んでみて
Read it.
Eggchanted Frog.
タマホマレガエル
The miraculous frog that surfaces but once every 16 years.
十六年に一度だけ地上に現れる奇跡な蛙
満月の夜　この蛙を十六歳男子の背中の上で産卵させ
Allow it to spawn eggs on the back of a 16-year-old boy under the full moon.
その卵を乾燥させてすり潰した粉薬は愛の妙薬
The crushed powder of its dried eggs is an elixir of love.
Man and woman who shared the elixir will be bound by eternal love.
男女が飲んだその二人は永遠の愛で結ばれる
Cool Story, Bro.
嘘くせい
There you go, take your top off.
というわけだから　脱いで
Huh?
You read it, right?
読んだでしょう　産卵させるのよ
We're making it spawn eggs.
What?!
You want the diary, right?
欲しいんでしょう　日記
For Himari.
ひまりちゃんのために
Don't you move!
動いちゃだめよ
That's strange.
おかしいわね　もう二時間も経つのに
It's been two hours.
It's not spawning at all!
全然生まないじゃない
For Himari... for Himari!
ひまりのためだ　ひまりのためだ
The ideal spawning temperature is 42°C.
なお　産卵の理想的な温度は四十二度
出来る
Can you do that?
出来ません
Nope.
For Himari...
ひまりのためだ　ひまりのためだ
For Himari!
For... Himari!
ひまりの　ため
Here it comes!
来た来た　もう少しよ
Almost...
Come on, almost there!
そうよ　もうちょっと
Something is coming out!
何が出で来た
嫌
No! No, yuck!
嫌々
怖い　怖い
It's scary!
The eggs?
卵
Huh?
あれ　あれ　卵は何処
Where did the eggs go?
They were there just now!
先までここにあったのに
Who knows?
さあ　何処にいちゃったんだろうね
I wonder where they went...
Survival Strategy!
生存戦略
Welcome to Rock'n Roll Night
Welcome to Rock'n Roll Fight
I'm just a Rock'n Roll Man
We're just a Rock'n Roll BAND
俺たちは道なりに　歩き続けてきた
標識だらけの道を飛ばし続けていく
幾つもの町を抜け　歌い続けてきた
腑抜け野郎共を煽り続けていく
長い長い冬が溶けても風が吹く
今も今も激しく風が吹く
Imagine!
Listen, you lowlifes who will never amount to anything.
きっと何物にもなれないお前たちに告げる
Obtain the Penguin Drum.
ピングドラムを手に入れるのだ
It's impossible now!
もう無理無理
Tabuki is already engaged to Yuri!
多蕗は百合さんと婚約しちゃったから
It's your job...
そこを何とかするのが
貴様らの役目であろう
to do something about it.
I'm sick of it. I've had enough of that occult psycho girl!
もう嫌だ
あんなおかれと再婚娘には付き合えない
It's not over yet.
まだ可能性はある
I hear men get marriage blues, too.
男にもマリッジブルー あるらしいぜ
So, you're saying?
要するに
Oginome Ringo wants to do adult stuff with Tabuki, right?
荻野目リンゴは多蕗とアダルトしたいってことだろう
まだそういう
Geez...
Tabuki is a man.
多蕗も男だ
If we plan this right, one night indiscression isn't out of the question.
そこうまく攻めれば
一夜の過ちってことも
Bro, stop with the evil look.
兄貴　その顔
Do it, Slave #2.
では　やれ　下僕二号
ええ　僕が
What? Me?!
You useless dimwit.
役立たずのおたんちんめ
Do it by any means.
手段を選ぶな
Seduce Tabuki into tapping Oginome Ringo!
多蕗を唆して荻野目リンゴとファイト一発
Don't make Himari say such a dirty thing!
そんな下品な言葉をひまりに言わねえななな
Let's inititate the Survival Strategy.
生存戦略　しましょうか
It was a mistake to depend on such an immoral method.
やっぱりいかがわしい方法に頼ったのが間違えたんだわ
No problem.
大丈夫　ここまで書いてあることは全部真実になったし
Everything written here has come true.
But why did Tabuki get engaged to that woman?
でも　どうして　多蕗さんはあんな女と
No, don't doubt yourself.
だめよ　弱気になちゃう
After all, the destiny belongs to Tabuki and me...
だって　運命は私と多蕗さんとそして桃果の物なんだから
And Momoka.
Please, give me one more chance!
どうかもう一度だけチャンスを
Ribbit.
The Prince and I are fated for each other... it's Destiny!
わたしと王子様は運命　デスティニーなのです
It's impossible for you!
あなたには無理ですわ
What?
Yuri!
ゆー　りー
Did you really think a dirty skank like you can rule the almighty Boulevards Dynasty?
貴方のような洟垂れの小娘に
この栄えあるブルバン王女が背を負えると思って
多蕗王子様はこの私とファビュラスマックス
Prince Tabuki and I are... Fabulous Max!
Oh, incredible beauty!
おう　なんという美しいさ
Prince!?
王子
No!
だめ
Ribbit.
ゲロ
No! Stop!
嫌　やめて
Show me you can bear his child if you can't stand losing to me.
そんなに口惜しいのなら
お譲りでも生んでみることね
Project M
Maternity Mission
Bear Tabuki's child...
多蕗さんの子を宿す
That's it!
そうよ　クリエーティブな愛の証よ
Just Married
The creative symbol of love!
When the future becomes true,
未来が真実になる時
my precious things will become eternal!
大切なものは永遠に
The Eggchanting Girl
subete ga moshi kimerarete tara
If everything was written in stone
全てが欲しい
繋がれたいたら
bokura wa doushite mogaku no darou
Why have we been resisting our fate?
僕らはどうして
もがくのだろう
それは君じゃない
sore wa kimi ja nai
It's not you
kimi no sei ja nai
It's not your fault
君のせいじゃない
苦しみはもう沢山なんだ
kanashimi wa mou takusan nanda
I've had enough misery
dakara sou ja nai
You're mistaken
だからそうじゃない
夢のままじゃない
ima no mama ja nai
Fate can be changed
umaku tsutaekirenai kedo
I can't explain it, but
上手く伝えきれないけど
Dear my future
Dear your future
Imagine!
これだけはしたくなかった
でももう時間がない
Listen, you lowlifes who will never amount to anything.
今夜　貴方に女の子の一番大切なものをあげる
Obtain the Blu-ray.
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
日听 xHunter 翻译：英英 校对：凌可乐
时间轴：绯桜闲   压制：笑眯眯的妖精
Let's initiate the Survival Strategy.
I wish it hadn't come to this.
But I'm running out of time!
Tonight, I'll give you my most important thing as a girl.
生存戦略　ファビュラス　マックス
Lily Hoshino